fontarsiv.com 2016-06-10

# Fontarsiv - Free Font Gallery

Privacy Policy

* * *

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### Visitor Tracking

We sometimes collect anonymous information through the use of various technologies, possibly including one called "cookies," to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on FontArsiv.com, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. This anonymous information is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data." FontArsiv.com or its analytic vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. Also, when we collect personal data, we may extract some information and combine it with other information, such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level.

If you do not want your personal information used in this manner, you can opt-out by clicking on the link to our "Contact Us" page. Cookies are small files that a Website installs on your hard drive. Cookies enable our Web server to recognize your computer. This allows a company to tailor its Websites to better match your interests and preferences. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the Websites visited just before and just after its Website. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to block cookies altogether. However, if you do so, your ability to use the Website may be impaired. Most browsers also allow you to erase cookies already stored.

### Security

FontArsiv.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Use of software author names, addresses and any other personal information is used only in our announcements and is not released to third parties nor do we send any mail to the return addresses offering or soliciting any services.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. FontArsiv.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via [online form.](http://www.fontarsiv.com/contact)
